Retractor.
Hemostat.
Sorry, doctor.
Since you obviously
need to practice,
put it back and
we'll try it again.
- It wasn't my fault...
- Hemostat!
I'm not interested in your excuses
or anything else you have to say.
So from now on, you
keep your mouth shut.
Scalpel. Let's go,
let's go, move it.
I'm moving as quickly
as safety allows.
All right, that's
it. Get out of here!
- You, take over, hurry up.
- Yes, doctor.
Scalpel.
What's going on?
Gray just kicked
me out of the O.R.
He was absolutely insufferable.
It's the divorce.
His wife's trying to squeeze
every dime she can out of him.
Well, bless her heart.
Insubordinate and incompetent.
I'm sick to death
of people like her.
It's okay, Bradley. She's gone.
She has no business
being anywhere near an O.R.
Good Lord, suction.
Suction.
- Hemostat.
- Sponge.
My God, her kidney's bleeding
like there's no tomorrow.
- Three units.
- I didn't go that deep, did I?
Looked to me
like you severed it.
So, what happens now?
Now we wait till the
patient's out of recovery.
- And then you tell her?
- Of course I tell her.
What did you think I was gonna
do? Let her walk out of here
with a damaged kidney,
hope she never noticed?
I'm sorry. I don't know
what the proper procedure is.
This is a first for me.
It's not exactly something
I do every day either.
I wasn't suggesting that it was.
Come on, Bradley, take it easy.
First thing we do
is tell the patient.
We meaning you and I,
so that nobody can say
that I misrepresented
the facts to her.
I take it back. That's the
second thing that we do.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- No.
It took him ten minutes
to stop the bleeding.
I mean, he just creamed it.
For all the good it's gonna do her
now, he may as well have just removed it.
Nurse Stone, your behavior in
the O.R. today was inexcusable.
By distracting me like that,
you cost a woman her kidney.
You're blaming me?
And after I speak to the administrator,
it will have cost you your job.
Oh...
Hello, Nancy.
This is Dr. Conway. He
assisted me during your surgery.
Actually, we met before,
just outside the O.R.
I know you probably don't
remember. You were a little loopy.
Oh, I was high as a kite. Heh.
So how you doing?
You tell me.
Well, your back is
gonna be just fine.
As I told you in your
pre-op appointment,
for the next few months,
you're gonna experience
some pain and lack of mobility,
but in time and
with proper exercise,
your back is gonna
be as good as new.
Unless, of course, you go
rupturing two more discs.
So, what's wrong?
Well...
In the course of the surgery,
I'm afraid that one of your
kidneys, the right one, was damaged.
What do you mean?
It was lacerated inadvertently.
As I told you, the kidneys
are in very close proximity
- to the surgical site...
- How bad is it?
Well, I can't say
with certainty,
but the kidney appears to be
rather severely compromised,
probably to the point
of being nonfunctional.
Oh...
Oh, my God, you mean I'm gonna
have to spend the rest of my life
hooked up to some kind of
dialysis machine or some...?
No. No, no, no.
- Nothing like that at all.
- No.
In all likelihood, you'll experience
no ill effects whatsoever.
That's right. Your left
kidney is more than capable
of taking care of
things all by itself.
People live long, happy, healthy
lives with only one kidney all the time.
What if something
happens to my left kidney?
Well, chances are nothing will.
Who did it? You?
No.
No, I'm afraid I'm responsible.
I was distracted at a
highly inopportune moment.
I'm sorry.
You destroy a perfectly
healthy part of my body,
and all you can
say is you're sorry?
There are risks associated
with all surgeries,
as I pointed out to you
when you signed your release.
I signed that release
because you led me to believe
that I was in the hands
of a highly skilled surgeon,
not some absent-minded butcher.
I'd be happy to recommend
a very good kidney specialist
- who can explain...
- No. No more doctors.
The only thing I want right now is
the name of a really good lawyer.
- Thanks for coming so soon...
- Hi.
- Heh. I thought you were the roofer.
- Oh.
Can I come in anyway?
Mom gave me this address.
Told me this is where you
spend most of your time.
Yeah, the man I
work for lives here,
and, uh, he works out
of his house, so I do too.
Oh...
For a second there I thought maybe
you're shacking up with somebody.
So, what are you doing here?
How come you're not at work?
I lost my job.
The hospital laid a bunch of
people off a couple months ago,
and I was one of them.
So I figured I had some spare
time, I'd come down for a visit.
And we'd do what?
Oh, I don't know.
Hang out, try to talk.
It's been a long time.
You didn't drive across two
states to come and visit me.
You never visited me
when you lived across town.
You didn't get laid off.
You got fired, didn't you?
So, what is it, Rachel,
you, uh...? You broke?
You need a handout?
God, I don't believe
this. You... Oh...
You know what ticks me
off the most about you?
It isn't the lying or your inability
to take responsibility for anything.
It's that you think so little of me, you
still believe you can get away with this.
Why do you always
think that I'm lying?
Rachel, you don't know
how to tell the truth.
- God, Jerri, that was a long time ago.
- You're always doctoring it up.
You're always twisting it
around to fit your little purposes.
Okay, you know what?
Forget it, just forget it.
I'm gonna go, and you are never
gonna hear from me again, all right?
How is that?
Trust me, I'll
never be that lucky!
Who was that?
- My sister.
- Oh.
Speed limit's the same here
as it is in North Carolina, ma'am.
My radar gun says
you were going 80.
Oh, no way I was
going that fast.
I mean, I didn't feel
like I was going that fast.
License and
registration, please.
Sure.
Put your hands on your head
and very slowly get out of the car.
What...?
What's going on?
There's an all-points
bulletin out on you.
You're wanted in
Wilmington, North Carolina,
for murder.
Case 95 48625-4-3.
The People v. Rachel Stone.
What are the charges?
The state charges that Rachel
Stone murdered Dr. Bradley Gray
on March 7th, 1995, with
premeditation, Your Honor.
Have you retained counsel?
I can't afford a lawyer.
Well, then one will
be supplied for you.
That won't be necessary,
Your Honor. I'll take it.
- It looked like you were fleeing.
- I wasn't fleeing.
I didn't even know
Dr. Gray was dead.
Why were you heading south?
I was going to Valdosta.
Cousin Martha just moved there.
And you were gonna hit
her up for some money.
- I was not.
- Why else would you go see her?
- You can't stand Cousin Martha.
- Oh, how the hell would you know?
- I know.
- All right, all right, all right.
Can we quit talking
about Cousin Martha?
Let's talk about Dr. Gray.
Dr. Gray was an orthopedic
surgeon at Shoreline General.
It was the hospital
that I worked.
He was a real egomaniac, I
mean, horrible to work with.
Anyway, about four months ago,
he accidentally damaged
a patient's kidney
during an operation I
assisted on, and he blamed me,
and he got me fired.
And this was not your
fault in the slightest?
That's right.
He fired you for no
reason? Come on, Rachel.
Oh, the guy made a mistake.
It cost his insurance
company 1.5 million bucks.
He had to blame
somebody, so he blamed me.
- Right, right.
- All right, all right, all right.
What about the scalpel the
police found in your house?
I have no idea
where that came from.
Somebody must've put it there after I
left for Atlanta, that's all I can figure.
Three people say
they saw you at the hospital
the day of the murder.
Did they?
Yeah, I've been looking
and looking for another job,
and no one would hire me
because Dr. Gray badmouthed me
to hospital administrators all over town.
So I went to see him.
I expected him to
give me a break.
And he what...?
Heh. Not a chance, no. Heh.
So I packed up my
car, I headed for Atlanta.
Figured a little help
from my only sister,
maybe I could start
over down there.
Wrong.
And this was the last time you
saw Dr. Gray since you were let go?
Yeah.
I should never have
gotten you into this.
- I am so sorry.
- What? What?
You had a loud
argument with Dr. Gray
outside the Parkway Grill
ten days before the murder.
- At least four people saw you.
- I forgot, I am sorry.
Rachel, we have gotta
get something straight here.
Mr. Matlock is one of the
best lawyers in this country.
He is doing this
as a favor to me,
but he cannot help you if
you don't tell him the truth.
We just happened to run
into each other, that's all.
He said something snotty to
me, I said something snotty to him.
That's all it was, it was nothing.
That's all. That's all it was, nothing.
Then you go see if you can
give us a look at the crime scene,
I'll take care of your sister.
- You better keep a polygraph handy.
- Go ahead.
- Oh, that's funny. That's really cute.
- Go ahead, go ahead. Okay, let's go.
He was only stabbed once?
One time, right
in that main artery.
Either the killer got lucky
or he knew his anatomy.
- Any fingerprints on the scalpel?
- No, latex.
Probably wore surgical gloves.
And since Rachel's a surgical
nurse, to say nothing of the fact
that the murder weapon
was found in her living room...
The prosecutor's gonna
have a field day, isn't he?
Well, I know I would.
My sister has her faults.
Well, all of us do.
But she'd never kill anybody.
It's not in her nature.
When we were kids...
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
- Have I got some interesting news.
- What?
Phone records. Guess
who Dr. Bradley Gray called
every day, at least
once a day, for weeks
- up until the day he was murdered.
- Who?
Nancy Pierson.
The girl whose kidney he damaged
during that operation
that got Rachel fired.
Wonder why.
- Aah!
- Oh.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Ah. Oh...
Are you...? Excuse me.
Are you Nancy Pierson?
- Yes, sir.
- Oh, I'm, uh...
I'm Ben Matlock.
I saw you weren't here, and I
just thought I'd sit down and wait.
And I guess I dozed off.
- Did I drool?
- Heh.
- No, you just snored.
- Oh, well...
Uh, anyway, I'm a lawyer,
and I'm representing the woman
who's accused of
murdering Bradley Gray.
And I wondered if we
could, uh, talk a few minutes.
Oh, certainly, I have
all the time in the world.
Oh. Ah.
- Oh.
- Uh-oh. Your back still bothering you?
Oh, not as bad as
it was, believe me.
Just knowing that I'll never have
to pick up another suitcase again
- helps immensely.
- Oh, that's right.
You used to work as a
ticket agent, didn't you?
Twelve years, throwing
luggage onto a conveyer belt.
One day I grabbed ahold of
an innocent-looking duffle bag,
- pulled and ruptured two discs.
- Ooh.
Tell me about it.
But Dr. Gray made it all better.
I lost a kidney in the process,
but I also gained more
than a million dollars,
- Ooh.
- So I'd say it all worked out.
Uh, did you talk to Dr. Gray
after you decided to sue?
That man... Must have called
me every day for a month.
- Why?
- Trying to get me to drop the lawsuit.
He kept ranting and raving about
how it was gonna ruin his reputation,
like I cared.
When did the insurance
company settle with you?
Um... I deposited
the check on the 6th.
That would've been the
day before he was murdered.
Does that mean something?
Probably not.
We can talk in here.
As long as it doesn't take too
long. I need to go on rounds.
- Oh, you're a resident?
- Third-year surgical resident, yes.
Oh, you got one of those
blood pressure gizmos in here.
Sphygmomanometer.
The technical name for
it, sphygmomanometer.
You know, the last
time I saw my doctor,
he said my pressure
was a little high.
- You were probably just nervous.
- Oh, I was. But I'm not now.
I'm here and you're here
and it's here, everything's here,
so how about it?
Mr. Matlock, we shouldn't
even be talking while I'm on duty.
Well, you can
take it while we talk.
It'll just take a second,
and I won't tell anybody.
Ah. I understand you're
the one who found the body.
Yes. It was quite a shock.
I imagine.
Well, what were you doing
at the hospital on your day off?
Well, I needed to get
some stuff from my locker.
I stopped in to see Bradley. We'd
had a couple of run-ins during the week,
- and I just wanted to clear the air.
- Run-ins?
Oh, just silly little arguments
about things that were
totally inconsequential.
And then this malpractice
case was making him crazy.
I mean, coming on top
of his divorce like that.
He just made sure that everyone
was just as miserable as he was.
Was he driving
his ex-wife crazy?
Oh, no, she was happy as a
clam. She got half his money
and made a beeline
for the Greek isles. Eh.
- Oh, what's the matter?
- I just couldn't hear the first time.
- We were talking.
- Oh.
Uh, I understand that
you assisted Dr. Gray
in the operation that
caused the malpractice suit.
That's right.
Was Rachel Stone to
blame for what happened?
Bradley allowed himself to be
distracted at a critical moment
and made a critical error.
No one was to blame but him.
- What? What?
- I'm done.
It's still high, isn't it?
Mr. Matlock, if you're worried
about your blood pressure,
I suggest you see
your regular doctor.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to go on rounds.
Well, you could give me a pill.
I guess you know who
came to see me today.
We need to talk.
Hello, doctor.
Dr. Conway.
What are you doing there?
That room is off-limits.
Well, uh, I know,
but I... I just...
Maybe you better give me that.
Why didn't you tell us?
Tell you what?
About the file that
was in Dr. Gray's office.
The one containing a memo
describing how he caught
you stealing painkillers
from the hospital dispensary.
The one he made you sign.
I made a copy of it.
The Trioxin wasn't for me.
It was for my boyfriend.
And I wasn't stealing.
I was gonna replace it.
- Oh, for heaven's sake.
- I wasn't stealing it, Jerri.
Dr. Gray believed me. That's
why he never reported it.
That memo was just his way of
making sure I'd never do it again.
That memo is going to
allow the prosecutor to say
that you killed him
not for revenge,
but so that nobody would
find out what you did.
Can't you see how that
makes everything worse?
I knew if anyone found
that memo it'd be a disaster.
You should've told me.
Did you ask Dr. Conway
to steal it for you?
He volunteered.
He's a really good friend.
I...
He did it because I
stole the drugs for him.
- Hello, Miss Pierson.
- Hello.
Let's see now. Here you
go. Saw you sitting out here.
- Thought I'd save you a trip to the box.
- Oh, well, that was nice. Thank you.
I guess you're a woman
of leisure now, huh?
- You betcha.
- It must be nice.
- How's the back?
- It's getting better every day.
Well, wish I could say
the same about mine.
- Heh. Y'all take care.
- Ha-ha.
Help!
I can't breathe.
Help! Please!
It was my first year of
residency. I was a basket case.
And I wasn't the only one. I mean,
everybody I knew was popping pills.
There's a big difference
between popping pills
and stealing them.
I was gonna have
Rachel replace them
as soon as I got the
prescription refilled.
And if Bradley Gray hadn't come
along, nobody would've been the wiser.
Oh. Did, uh, he know that you were
the one she was stealing them for?
Not stealing, borrowing.
And no, she never told him.
So I had no reason to kill
him, if that's what this is about.
It was in the back of my mind.
- Now, you and Rachel are, uh...?
- Friends.
Friends.
She's a good person.
I was furious when
Bradley Gray had her fired,
but there was
nothing I could do.
- Tell you one thing though.
- Mm.
When I had to testify against
him in that malpractice case,
I enjoyed the hell out of it.
Oh, by the way,
I made an appointment
with my regular doctor.
- You know, about my blood pressure.
- Oh, good for you.
I made an appointment.
It was high, wasn't it?
Now, Mr. Matlock...
You know, sometimes I
get this throbbing headache
when I stand up real fast.
That's high blood
pressure, isn't it?
- Give me the vitals.
- Blood pressure 90/40,
pulse irregular,
airways constricted.
Was fine one minute,
next she couldn't breathe.
- Possible anaphylactic shock.
- Ten cc's of epinephrine.
Do blood gases,
evacuate her stomach.
Clear the hall! Keep
it down, move it!
Mrs. Pierson.
This is police
detective Hal Remsen.
Mr. Matlock here thought
it would be a good idea
if you told him
what you just told us.
Now, do you feel up to it?
Um, yeah, I guess.
She's a very lucky woman.
Hello, Miss Pierson.
You wanna tell me what happened?
Well, you see, I'm violently
allergic to benzocaine.
That's a painkiller,
prescription only.
Anyway, I took a garlic
pill right after lunch,
like I always do,
and next thing I
knew I was here.
We pumped her stomach.
We found remnants of Chinese
food and the garlic capsule,
which appears to have been laced
with a potentially fatal
dose of benzocaine.
How do you know the benzocaine
wasn't already in the food?
Well, she would've gone
into anaphylactic shock
right after the first bite.
Probably be dead now.
It was leftover moo goo gai
pan from the Lotus Garden.
They wouldn't poison me.
I'm too good a tipper.
Where did you get
the garlic capsules?
Mother Earth health food store.
I keep a bottle of
them in my purse.
It's supposed to prevent cancer.
How many people know
you're allergic to benzocaine?
A few.
Any of them particularly
mad at you for any reason?
Not that I know of.
Dr. Gray was pretty
mad. Very mad.
All those phone calls.
That's the doctor she
sued for malpractice.
Dr. Bradley Gray?
The man your client is
accused of having murdered?
Yeah.
So, what you're suggesting then
is that he put the benzocaine in
the capsules before he was killed?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you could say
that's what I'm saying.
Hi. So, what's for dinner?
- Stir-fry.
- Mm.
- Any chance we can add a little...?
- No, Jerri, no meat.
Oh, come on.
One chicken breast
is not gonna kill you.
Jerri, I do not want the flesh of
dead animals in my refrigerator.
Jeez, Rachel, I'm your guest.
Guest? You're my sister.
Explain something to me.
We are, we're sisters,
yet we fight all the time.
I mean, what happened to us?
We used to get along so well.
We did?
Yeah, remember when Mom
and Dad used to fight sometimes,
we used to run upstairs and
we used to hide under my bed?
No. You'd hide under your
bed, I'd hide under mine.
Well, that's not
how I remember it.
Rachel, you and I fought
every waking moment
of our childhood.
If we'd hid under a bed together,
one of us would've ended up dead
within about two minutes.
See? Why is that?
I don't know.
You and I are so different.
I see things one way, you
see things another way.
Only you have no
respect for my opinion,
and I don't care for yours.
It's always been that way.
So I guess we just don't
like each other, do we?
Hello?
In the kitchen.
Well, they're going to keep
Nancy Pierson under observation.
That's in case she
goes into shock again.
- Mm-hm.
- Happens sometimes.
Any idea who slipped
her the benzocaine?
I think it was Dr. Gray.
- Ben, that's crazy.
- No, it's not.
I mean, if she was allergic to penicillin
and wore a medical alert bracelet,
that's something anybody
who met her would know.
But to be allergic
to benzocaine?
That's something very few
people would know about.
Her doctor would.
Especially if he was
treating her for back pain.
Wait a minute.
Are you suggesting
that a renowned orthopedic
surgeon broke into her house
to tamper with her garlic pills?
If he wanted to kill her,
why go to such lengths?
Well, you're probably right.
So when are you gonna
go check out his house?
Uh, Cliff's, uh, working
out the arrangements now.
I'm gonna meet him
in about 30 minutes.
Of course I could be a little
late if dinner's about ready.
It's stir-fry. You're
welcome to stay.
She puts tofu in it, Ben.
No beef, no chicken, no fish.
Just vegetables and white gunk.
Oh, well, I probably
shouldn't keep Cliff waiting.
He moved in after the divorce.
It's nice enough.
Oh, you should've seen
the house he lived in before.
Right on the water, gorgeous view,
built-in vacuum-cleaning system.
Mm-mm-mm.
Mrs. Gray made him sell it so
she could get her half of the money.
Ah. Well, it's mighty clean.
You do awfully good work.
Oh, thank you. But to be
honest, he never got it very dirty.
I don't think he spent
that much time here.
Well, how often do you come in?
Mondays, Wednesdays and Fridays.
Mm...
Hm.
This bed doesn't look
like it's been slept in.
- When did you change the sheets?
- Last Monday.
I always did the
linens on Monday.
He was killed the next day.
Must have spent the
night somewheres else.
- Maybe he stayed at the hospital.
- Yeah.
Did Dr. Gray have a girlfriend?
I'm sure he dated.
Sometimes I could
smell a little perfume.
- Ah. But you never saw her?
- Never.
Heh. Sure didn't spend a lot
of time cooking, that's for sure.
Aha.
I guess he ate a lot
of takeout. Look at this.
Willard's Rib House, Lotus
Garden, Wilmington Grill...
- What was that Chinese?
- Lotus Garden.
Hi.
Can I come in?
Sure.
Thanks.
- How are you doing?
- I feel fine.
I don't know why
they're keeping me here.
Well, the reason I stopped by is I
was at Bradley Gray's apartment,
and, uh, I think
he had a girlfriend.
- Good for him.
- And I found out
that he likes Chinese food.
He ordered out from,
uh, Lotus Garden a lot.
What a coincidence.
I don't think so.
And just what do you think?
That girlfriend I mentioned,
I think that was you.
Oh, you can't be serious.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's how he knew
you take garlic pills.
That's how he could
get to your purse so easy
to lace one of them
with benzocaine.
Explains the phone calls.
He wasn't mad at
you. Quite the opposite.
The two of you were in bed together,
in more ways than one, weren't you?
You are out of your mind.
Sooner or later,
somebody's gonna remember
seeing the two of you together.
And the whole
thing's gonna crumble.
If I were you, I'd
let it go right now.
I'm sorry, but you're
really starting to annoy me.
Of course, I can, uh,
stop by your townhouse
and see what I find there.
You go near my place,
I'll have you arrested.
Yes?
Would you please come down here?
There's a man in here bothering me.
Of course, I can
always get a warrant.
You can go to
hell. Now, get out.
Okay.
So the scalpel was just
lying here in plain sight?
Police found it on the floor
by the corner of that chair.
Oh, does it really
make sense to them
that I would kill somebody, then
just leave a bloody murder weapon
- lying around my living room?
- They don't care.
It's our job to try
to make sense of it.
Did you lock all your
doors when you left?
- Always.
- Windows?
When I left town that day,
everything was locked and closed.
- Hm.
- You must've left something open.
How else could Nancy Pierson
have planted the scalpel in here?
I mean, it's not like she's
a professional burglar.
What about that?
Oh, yeah, that's the only
thing that wasn't locked.
But it doesn't count.
It's permanently stuck.
That's as far as it'll open.
I guess she could've jumped up,
caught the sill and pulled herself up.
- No, not with her back, she couldn't.
- Mm.
But maybe she could've...
Maybe she could've
stood on this.
That's where I keep
my gardening tools.
Oh, no. How'd it
get broken like that?
Ben, is that what I think it is?
And so, what went wrong during
the operation, Miss Pierson?
Dr. Gray accidentally
sliced open my right kidney
and virtually destroyed it.
And so, what did
you do as a result?
- I sued for malpractice.
- Oh.
And, uh, what were you awarded?
One and a half million dollars.
Boy, that's a lot of money
even when you say it fast.
Especially when you see that
you're not exactly incapacitated.
I'll be extremely incapacitated
if anything happens
to my other kidney.
Yeah, but the chances
are that nothing ever will,
and that's why you
and Dr. Gray decided
that this would be a
good gamble to take.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm saying that Dr. Bradley Gray
deliberately destroyed your kidney
so that you and he could
become $1.5 million richer.
Objection, Your Honor.
Mr. Matlock has just given new
meaning to the word "speculation."
Your Honor, it
would be speculation
if I didn't have
proof, but I do.
There's proof right here.
- Overruled.
- Excellent.
Uh, what's your phone
number, uh, Miss Pierson?
Five-five-five-seven-eight-six-eight.
Mm-hm.
I had the, uh... I had
the phone company
make a list of all the calls
Dr. Gray dialed from
his house and his office
in the five months prior to
his death in order of frequency.
Would you read the
number at the top of the list?
The one most often called.
"Five-five-five-seven-eight-six-eight."
- That's your number.
- Yes, but I told you...
And this card was on his
desk at Shoreline Hospital.
Would you tell the court
what that card represents?
- Gentle Giant Movers.
- Mm-hm.
Thank you. I wondered what
that was doing on his desk,
so I called them.
And guess what.
Dr. Gray had called
them too on March 6th,
the day before he was murdered.
And the man he spoke
to is Mr. C.J. Nussbaum.
And he is prepared to testify
that Mr. Gray did not call
because he was
thinking of moving.
He called him to find
out if a friend of his was.
A friend named Nancy Pierson.
You were gonna pack
up bag and baggage
and move to Dallas, weren't you?
Only you were gonna keep it a
secret from your friend, Dr. Gray,
because you had decided
to keep all 1.5 million
yourself, hadn't you?
He was not my friend.
He called me all those
times to harass me.
He must've called
the moving company
so that he could continue to
harass me even after I left town.
No. No.
At some point... At some point,
you and he got, you know, close.
And everybody
needs a little money.
He needed money
because of his divorce,
and so you and he
hatched up this scheme
to defraud his insurance
company of a small fortune
for sacrificing one
of your kidneys.
But then you got to
thinking about that thing.
"Wait a minute,
fair's fair here."
And you decided to keep it all.
But he found out.
And he said,
"Well, if I can't
have some of it,
she's not gonna have it either."
- No.
- And it almost worked.
He put something that
you are deathly allergic to
into one of those garlic
pills that you always take.
He couldn't tell anybody
what you had done,
because then they'd
know what he had done.
You were double-crossing him,
and he was helpless
to do anything about it.
So he decided to kill you.
He figured you wouldn't take
that garlic pill till you got to Dallas.
And he had no idea, he
didn't think for a minute,
that you would kill him first.
Objection.
Your Honor, I got
the proof right here.
Proceed.
Thank you.
This box was found beside
the defendant's house.
And there's a little window
that won't close all the way
anymore because the frame is warped.
You stood on that box
and dropped that scalpel
through that little opening
into Rachel Stone's
house, didn't you?
No, I did not.
You've never been to
Rachel Stone's house?
Of course not. I don't
even know where she lives.
But since her name came
up during that malpractice suit,
- you knew who she was, didn't you?
- Yes, but...
And you knew
that Dr. Gray had
caused her to be fired.
And you knew she'd
be a perfect one to frame
because everybody would
think that she killed him
because he fired her.
That's just not true.
And so you eased
in that hospital,
and you stole a pair
of gloves and a scalpel
from the supply room.
And then you killed Dr. Gray,
then you looked up Rachel's
address and went over to her house,
- didn't you?
- No.
Walked around her house,
walked around looking
for a way to get in.
And then you saw...
You saw that little window.
But it was 8 feet
above the ground.
So you drug over this box,
being very careful not
to hurt your back again.
And you stood on it,
and you dropped that bloody scalpel
through the window into her house.
Then you went home,
postponed your trip to Dallas
till the coast was absolutely clear.
No, no. None...
None of this is true.
Yes, it is.
You know how I know?
Because when you stepped
on this box to reach the window,
you broke it, didn't
you? See that?
Remember?
See, your foot went all
the way through that slat.
See there, you can see
your blood on the wood.
See there?
And the police found
good skin samples too.
It wasn't me.
Then prove it.
- What do you mean?
- Let us see your legs.
I don't mean all the way up.
Just the calves.
You're wearing slacks
anyhow. Just pull them up.
If your legs have no
scratches on them,
you're home free.
I think that's a
reasonable request.
I'd like to talk to
a lawyer, please.
Good idea.
Whoo! Ha-ha-ha!
This is great. Heh.
I haven't felt this free
since I went topless
- at Lollapalooza last summer. Ha-ha!
- Ooh. Heh-heh.
- Thanks for everything.
- Oh.
Don't thank me. It was your sister
who made us come to the rescue.
Thank her.
Here I thought
you didn't like me.
It's not that I don't like you.
I think I'm harder on you
because you're my sister.
Come on.
I called the roofers
this morning.
- They're done, so we'll be going home.
- Oh, good.
- You're welcome to come with us.
- Oh, thanks, but I gotta find a job.
Know anybody who needs a nurse?
Speaking of that nursing and
all, when I stand up real fast,
I get dizzy and kind
of get a headache.
Is that high blood pressure?
www.tvsubtitles.net